Guide to the Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 3, Section 2: Boxes 23-44
Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 3, Section 2: Boxes 23-44
- Box: 27, Folder: 69, Publication (Box 27, Folder 69)
  - Item 1: Master Organization Chart, 1969; Publication (Box 27, Folder 69)
- Box: 27, Folder: 70, Publication (Box 27, Folder 70)
  - Item 1: Alumnus Gift- Matching Program: Regulations and Forms, 1969; Publication (Box 27, Folder 70)
- Box: 27, Folder: 71, Publication (Box 27, Folder 71)
  - Item 1: Employee Educational Assistance Program, 1968; Publication (Box 27, Folder 71)
- Box: 27, Folder: 72, Publication (Box 27, Folder 72)
  - Item 1: Merit Scholarships For Sons of Employees, 1969; Publication (Box 27, Folder 72)
- Box: 27, Folder: 73, Publication (Box 27, Folder 73)
  - Item 1: Suggestion Systems, 1959; Publication (Box 27, Folder 73)
- Box: 27, Folder: 74, Publication (Box 27, Folder 74)
  - Item 1: Alumnus Gift- Matching Program: Regulations and Forms, 1972; Publication (Box 27, Folder 74)
- Box: 27, Folder: 75, Publication (Box 27, Folder 75)
  - Item 1: Employee Educational Assistance Program, 1971; Publication (Box 27, Folder 75)
- Box: 27, Folder: 76, Publication (Box 27, Folder 76)
  - Item 1: Scholarship Program For Children of Employees, 1971; Publication (Box 27, Folder 76)
- Box: 27, Folder: 77, Publication (Box 27, Folder 77)
  - Item 1: Master Organization Chart, 1972; Publication (Box 27, Folder 77)
- Box: 27, Folder: 78, Publication (Box 27, Folder 78)
  - Item 1: Employee Recruiting, 1969; Publication (Box 27, Folder 78)
- Box: 27, Folder: 79, Publication (Box 27, Folder 79)
  - Item 1: Scholarship Program For Sons Of Employees, 1957; Publication (Box 27, Folder 79)
- Box: 27, Folder: 80, Publication (Box 27, Folder 80)
  - Item 1: Employee Educational Assistance Program, 1956; Publication (Box 27, Folder 80)
- Box: 27, Folder: 81, Publication (Box 27, Folder 81)
  - Item 1: Suggestion System, 1955; Publication (Box 27, Folder 81)
- Box: 27, Folder: 82, Publication (Box 27, Folder 82)
  - Item 1: Work Simplification Plan, 1955; Publication (Box 27, Folder 82)
- Box: 27, Folder: 83, Publication (Box 27, Folder 83)
  - Item 1: Master Organization Chart, 1962; Publication (Box 27, Folder 83)
- Box: 27, Folder: 84, Publication (Box 27, Folder 84)
  - Item 1: Employee Recruiting, 1963; Publication (Box 27, Folder 84)
- Box: 27, Folder: 85, Publication (Box 27, Folder 85)
  - Item 1: Management Committee, Publication (Box 27, Folder 85)
- Box: 27, Folder: 86, Publication (Box 27, Folder 86)
  - Item 1: Application For Employment, 1942; Publication (Box 27, Folder 86)
- Box: 27, Folder: 87, Publication (Box 27, Folder 87)
  - Item 1: Employee Educational Assistance, Publication (Box 27, Folder 87)
- Box: 27, Folder: 88, Publication (Box 27, Folder 88)
  - Item 1: Collective Bargaining, 1956; Publication (Box 27, Folder 88)
- Box: 27, Folder: 89, Publication (Box 27, Folder 89)
  - Item 1: Alumnus Gift- Matching Program: Regulations and Forms, 1956; Publication (Box 27, Folder 89)
- Box: 27, Folder: 90, Publication (Box 27, Folder 90)
  - Item 1: Scholarship Application For Sons of Employees, 1963; Publication (Box 27, Folder 90)
- Box: 27, Folder: 91, Publication (Box 27, Folder 91)
  - Item 1: Master Organization Chart, 1966; Publication (Box 27, Folder 91)
- Box: 27, Folder: 92, Publication (Box 27, Folder 92)
  - Item 1: Alumnus Gift- Matching Program: Regulations and Forms, 1960; Publication (Box 27, Folder 92)
- Box: 27, Folder: 93, Publication (Box 27, Folder 93)
  - Item 1: Alumnus Gift- Matching Program: Regulations and Forms, 1963; Publication (Box 27, Folder 93)
- Box: 27, Folder: 94, Publication (Box 27, Folder 94)
  - Item 1: Employee Educational Assistance Program, 1963; Publication (Box 27, Folder 94)
- Box: 27, Folder: 95, Publication (Box 27, Folder 95)
  - Item 1: Accident Prevention, 1957; Publication (Box 27, Folder 95)
- Box: 27, Folder: 96, Publication (Box 27, Folder 96)
  - Item 1: Training, 1956; Publication (Box 27, Folder 96)
- Box: 27, Folder: 97, Publication (Box 27, Folder 97)
  - Item 1: Management Inventory and Development Program, 1961; Publication (Box 27, Folder 97)
- Box: 27, Folder: 98, Publication (Box 27, Folder 98)
  - Item 1: Supplemental Information Pamphlets, Publication (Box 27, Folder 98)
- Box: 27, Folder: 99, Publication (Box 27, Folder 99)
  - Item 1: Training, Publication (Box 27, Folder 99)
- Box: 27, Folder: 100, Publication (Box 27, Folder 100)
  - Item 1: Tuition Assistance, 1972; Publication (Box 27, Folder 100)
- Box: 27, Folder: 101, Publication (Box 27, Folder 101)
  - Item 1: Your Matching Education Gifts Program, Publication (Box 27, Folder 101)
- Box: 27, Folder: 102, Publication (Box 27, Folder 102)
  - Item 1: Newsletter, 1964; Publication (Box 27, Folder 102)
- Box: 27, Folder: 103, Publication (Box 27, Folder 103)
  - Item 1: Training, 1967; Publication (Box 27, Folder 103)
- Box: 27, Folder: 104, Publication (Box 27, Folder 104)
  - Item 1: The Steelworkers' Institutes, 1955; Publication (Box 27, Folder 104)
- Box: 27, Folder: 105, Publication (Box 27, Folder 105)
  - Item 1: United Steelworkers Long Range Sharing, 1964; Publication (Box 27, Folder 105)
- Box: 27, Folder: 106, Publication (Box 27, Folder 106)
  - Item 1: Management Responsibilities, 1954; Publication (Box 27, Folder 106)
- Box: 27, Folder: 107, Publication (Box 27, Folder 107)
  - Item 1: General Safety Manual, Publication (Box 27, Folder 107)
- Box: 27, Folder: 108, Publication (Box 27, Folder 108)
  - Item 1: Handbook, 1953; Publication (Box 27, Folder 108)
- Box: 27, Folder: 109, Publication (Box 27, Folder 109)
  - Item 1: Supervisory Conference Leader's Guide, 1952; Publication (Box 27, Folder 109)
- Box: 27, Folder: 110, Publication (Box 27, Folder 110)
  - Item 1: Management Trainee Program, 1962; Publication (Box 27, Folder 110)
- Box: 27, Folder: 111, Publication (Box 27, Folder 111)
  - Item 1: Employee Recruiting, 1954; Publication (Box 27, Folder 111)
- Box: 27, Folder: 112, Publication (Box 27, Folder 112)
  - Item 1: Wasting Away, 1954; Publication (Box 27, Folder 112)
- Box: 27, Folder: 113, Publication (Box 27, Folder 113)
  - Item 1: Company History, 1962; Publication (Box 27, Folder 113)
- Box: 27, Folder: 114, Publication (Box 27, Folder 114)
  - Item 1: Your Side Of The Counter, 1954; Publication (Box 27, Folder 114)
- Box: 27, Folder: 115, Publication (Box 27, Folder 115)
  - Item 1: C.S. Means Capable Saleslady, 1954; Publication (Box 27, Folder 115)
- Box: 27, Folder: 116, Publication (Box 27, Folder 116)
  - Item 1: Brief History, 1956; Publication (Box 27, Folder 116)
- Box: 27, Folder: 117, Publication (Box 27, Folder 117)
  - Item 1: Training Report On Assistant Manager, 1954; Publication (Box 27, Folder 117)
- Box: 27, Folder: 118, Publication (Box 27, Folder 118)
  - Item 1: Vacations, 1954; Publication (Box 27, Folder 118)
- Box: 27, Folder: 119, Publication (Box 27, Folder 119)
  - Item 1: Employee Recruiting, 1968; Publication (Box 27, Folder 119)
- Box: 27, Folder: 120, Publication (Box 27, Folder 120)
  - Item 1: Brief History, 1968; Publication (Box 27, Folder 120)
- Box: 27, Folder: 121, Publication (Box 27, Folder 121)
  - Item 1: Annual Report 1968, Publication (Box 27, Folder 121)
- Box: 27, Folder: 122, Publication (Box 27, Folder 122)
  - Item 1: Organization Chart, 1953; Publication (Box 27, Folder 122)
- Box: 27, Folder: 123, Publication (Box 27, Folder 123)
  - Item 1: Limited Leave Of Absence, 1954; Publication (Box 27, Folder 123)
- Box: 27, Folder: 124, Publication (Box 27, Folder 124)
  - Item 1: Men And Women Entering The Armed Forces, 1954; Publication (Box 27, Folder 124)
- Box: 27, Folder: 125, Publication (Box 27, Folder 125)
  - Item 1: Suggestion System, 1954; Publication (Box 27, Folder 125)
- Box: 27, Folder: 126, Publication (Box 27, Folder 126)
  - Item 1: Industrial Organization, 1956; Publication (Box 27, Folder 126)
- Box: 27, Folder: 127, Publication (Box 27, Folder 127)
  - Item 1: Employee Recruiting, 1962; Publication (Box 27, Folder 127)
- Box: 27, Folder: 128, Publication (Box 27, Folder 128)
  - Item 1: Organization Chart, 1961; Publication (Box 27, Folder 128)
- Box: 27, Folder: 129, Publication (Box 27, Folder 129)
  - Item 1: Surgical Benefit Certificate, 1949; Publication (Box 27, Folder 129)
- Box: 27, Folder: 130, Publication (Box 27, Folder 130)
  - Item 1: Suggestion Systems, 1951; Publication (Box 27, Folder 130)
- Box: 27, Folder: 131, Publication (Box 27, Folder 131)
  - Item 1: Report On D.O. Employees, 1940; Publication (Box 27, Folder 131)
- Box: 27, Folder: 132, Publication (Box 27, Folder 132)
  - Item 1: Profit Sharing, 1925; Publication (Box 27, Folder 132)
- Box: 27, Folder: 133, Publication (Box 27, Folder 133)
  - Item 1: Letter To Mr. J. Douglas Brown, 1927; Publication (Box 27, Folder 133)
- Box: 27, Folder: 134, Publication (Box 27, Folder 134)
  - Item 1: Employment Forms, 1940; Publication (Box 27, Folder 134)
- Box: 27, Folder: 135, Publication (Box 27, Folder 135)
  - Item 1: Organization Chart, 1951; Publication (Box 27, Folder 135)
- Box: 27, Folder: 136, Publication (Box 27, Folder 136)
  - Item 1: Profit Sharing, 1953; Publication (Box 27, Folder 136)
- Box: 27, Folder: 137, Publication (Box 27, Folder 137)
  - Item 1: Safety, 1969; Publication (Box 27, Folder 137)
- Box: 27, Folder: 138, Publication (Box 27, Folder 138)
  - Item 1: Profit Sharing, 1966; Publication (Box 27, Folder 138)
- Box: 27, Folder: 139, Publication (Box 27, Folder 139)
  - Item 1: Mutual Benefit Association, 1966; Publication (Box 27, Folder 139)
- Box: 27, Folder: 140, Publication (Box 27, Folder 140)
  - Item 1: Employee's Profit Sharing Plan, 1956; Publication (Box 27, Folder 140)
- Box: 27, Folder: 141, Publication (Box 27, Folder 141)
  - Item 1: Job Evaluation Program, Publication (Box 27, Folder 141)
- Box: 27, Folder: 142, Publication (Box 27, Folder 142)
  - Item 1: Profit Sharing Plan, 1951; Publication (Box 27, Folder 142)
- Box: 27, Folder: 143, Publication (Box 27, Folder 143)
  - Item 1: Courses For Management, 1956; Publication (Box 27, Folder 143)
- Box: 27, Folder: 144, Publication (Box 27, Folder 144)
  - Item 1: Management Development Guide, Publication (Box 27, Folder 144)
- Box: 27, Folder: 145, Publication (Box 27, Folder 145)
  - Item 1: Manual Of Personnel Practice, 1968; Publication (Box 27, Folder 145)
- Box: 28, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Merchandising And Operations Management Development, 1965; Publication (Box 28, Folder 1)
- Box: 28, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Accounting Management Training Plan, 1965; Publication (Box 28, Folder 2)
- Box: 28, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Warehouse And Transportation Management Training Plan, 1965; Publication (Box 28, Folder 3)
- Box: 28, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Management Development Plan, 1960; Publication (Box 28, Folder 4)
- Box: 28, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Management Development Plan, 1962; Publication (Box 28, Folder 5)
- Box: 28, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Management Improvement Project, 1966; Publication (Box 28, Folder 6)
- Box: 28, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Management Improvement Project, 1960; Publication (Box 28, Folder 7)
- Box: 28, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Management Development Plan, 1962; Publication (Box 28, Folder 8)
- Box: 28, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Checker Training: Book I, 1965; Publication (Box 28, Folder 9)
- Box: 28, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Checker Training Book III, 1965; Publication (Box 28, Folder 10)
- Box: 28, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Checker Training Book IV, 1965; Publication (Box 28, Folder 11)
- Box: 28, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Checker Training Book V, 1965; Publication (Box 28, Folder 12)
- Box: 28, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Management Improvement Project, 1960; Publication (Box 28, Folder 13)
- Box: 28, Folder: 14, Publication (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Working At Kroger, Publication (Box 28, Folder 14)
- Box: 28, Folder: 15, Publication (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Acceptable Price-Marking, 1965; Publication (Box 28, Folder 15)
- Box: 28, Folder: 16, Publication (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Basic Stock, 1965; Publication (Box 28, Folder 16)
- Box: 28, Folder: 17, Publication (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Checker Training Book II, 1965; Publication (Box 28, Folder 17)
- Box: 29, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Life Insurance Plan, 1971; Publication (Box 29, Folder 1)
- Box: 29, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Managerial Major Medical Insurance, 1971; Publication (Box 29, Folder 2)
- Box: 29, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Your Continuation Of Income Plan, 1971; Publication (Box 29, Folder 3)
- Box: 29, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Income For Your Retirement Years, 1971; Publication (Box 29, Folder 4)
- Box: 29, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Income For Your Retirement Years, 1971; Publication (Box 29, Folder 5)
- Box: 29, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Income For Your Retirement Years, 1971; Publication (Box 29, Folder 6)
- Box: 29, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Your Share Of Lever Products, 1970; Publication (Box 29, Folder 7)
- Box: 29, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Public Relations, 1951; Publication (Box 29, Folder 8)
- Box: 29, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Hospital, Surgical, Medical and Major Medical Insurance, 1971; Publication (Box 29, Folder 9)
- Box: 29, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Protection For You and Your Family, 1963; Publication (Box 29, Folder 10)
- Box: 29, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Industrial Relations Course, Publication (Box 29, Folder 11)
- Box: 29, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Bulletin, 1956; Publication (Box 29, Folder 12)
- Box: 29, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: How To Find What You File, 1958; Publication (Box 29, Folder 13)
- Box: 29, Folder: 14, Publication (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Monthly Information Bulletin, 1950; Publication (Box 29, Folder 14)
- Box: 29, Folder: 15, Publication (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Interview, Publication (Box 29, Folder 15)
- Box: 29, Folder: 16, Publication (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Your Lever Security Package, 1966; Publication (Box 29, Folder 16)
- Box: 29, Folder: 17, Publication (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Interview, 1938; Publication (Box 29, Folder 17)
    Author: F>H. Harbison
- Box: 29, Folder: 18, Publication (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Industrial Organization Chart, 1952; Publication (Box 29, Folder 18)
- Box: 29, Folder: 19, Publication (Box 29, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Management Chart, 1953; Publication (Box 29, Folder 19)
- Box: 29, Folder: 20, Publication (Box 29, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Management Chart, 1953; Publication (Box 29, Folder 20)
- Box: 29, Folder: 21, Publication (Box 29, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: Report On Probationary Employees, 1956; Publication (Box 29, Folder 21)
- Box: 29, Folder: 22, Publication (Box 29, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: Company Policy Manual, 1957; Publication (Box 29, Folder 22)
- Box: 29, Folder: 23, Publication (Box 29, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: Industrial Organization Chart, 1965; Publication (Box 29, Folder 23)
- Box: 29, Folder: 24, Publication (Box 29, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: Industrial Organization Chart, 1961; Publication (Box 29, Folder 24)
- Box: 29, Folder: 25, Publication (Box 29, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: Industrial Organization Chart, 1977; Publication (Box 29, Folder 25)
- Box: 29, Folder: 26, Publication (Box 29, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: Industrial Organization Chart, 1975; Publication (Box 29, Folder 26)
- Box: 29, Folder: 27, Publication (Box 29, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: Building For The Future, 1963; Publication (Box 29, Folder 27)
- Box: 29, Folder: 28, Publication (Box 29, Folder 28)
  - Item 1: Security Package, 1952; Publication (Box 29, Folder 28)
- Box: 29, Folder: 29, Publication (Box 29, Folder 29)
  - Item 1: Security Package, 1957; Publication (Box 29, Folder 29)
- Box: 29, Folder: 30, Publication (Box 29, Folder 30)
  - Item 1: Handbook, 1948; Publication (Box 29, Folder 30)
- Box: 29, Folder: 31, Publication (Box 29, Folder 31)
  - Item 1: Retirement Plan- Salaried Employees, 1964; Publication (Box 29, Folder 31)
- Box: 29, Folder: 32, Publication (Box 29, Folder 32)
  - Item 1: Wage Agreements, 1955; Publication (Box 29, Folder 32)
- Box: 29, Folder: 33, Publication (Box 29, Folder 33)
  - Item 1: Handbook, 1951; Publication (Box 29, Folder 33)
- Box: 29, Folder: 34, Publication (Box 29, Folder 34)
  - Item 1: Scholarship Plan, 1957; Publication (Box 29, Folder 34)
- Box: 29, Folder: 35, Publication (Box 29, Folder 35)
  - Item 1: Newspaper Article, 1955; Publication (Box 29, Folder 35)
- Box: 29, Folder: 36, Publication (Box 29, Folder 36)
  - Item 1: Safety Rules, 1952; Publication (Box 29, Folder 36)
- Box: 29, Folder: 37, Publication (Box 29, Folder 37)
  - Item 1: Purpose And Goals Of The Industrial Relations Department, 1949; Publication (Box 29, Folder 37)
- Box: 29, Folder: 38, Publication (Box 29, Folder 38)
  - Item 1: Safety Rules, 1952; Publication (Box 29, Folder 38)
- Box: 29, Folder: 39, Publication (Box 29, Folder 39)
  - Item 1: Leave Of Absence, 1951; Publication (Box 29, Folder 39)
- Box: 29, Folder: 40, Publication (Box 29, Folder 40)
  - Item 1: Agreement, 1947; Publication (Box 29, Folder 40)
- Box: 29, Folder: 41, Publication (Box 29, Folder 41)
  - Item 1: Personnel Administration, 1966; Publication (Box 29, Folder 41)
- Box: 29, Folder: 42, Publication (Box 29, Folder 42)
  - Item 1: Artificial Respiration, 1960; Publication (Box 29, Folder 42)
- Box: 29, Folder: 43, Publication (Box 29, Folder 43)
  - Item 1: Accident Prevention, 1960; Publication (Box 29, Folder 43)
- Box: 29, Folder: 44, Publication (Box 29, Folder 44)
  - Item 1: Wage Rates, 1960; Publication (Box 29, Folder 44)
- Box: 29, Folder: 45, Publication (Box 29, Folder 45)
  - Item 1: Wage Rates, 1960; Publication (Box 29, Folder 45)
- Box: 29, Folder: 46, Publication (Box 29, Folder 46)
  - Item 1: Wage Rates, 1959; Publication (Box 29, Folder 46)
- Box: 29, Folder: 47, Publication (Box 29, Folder 47)
  - Item 1: Wage Relations, 1960; Publication (Box 29, Folder 47)
- Box: 29, Folder: 48, Publication (Box 29, Folder 48)
  - Item 1: Personnel Record Job Instruction Manual, 1960; Publication (Box 29, Folder 48)
- Box: 29, Folder: 49, Publication (Box 29, Folder 49)
  - Item 1: Recreation, 1960; Publication (Box 29, Folder 49)
- Box: 29, Folder: 50, Publication (Box 29, Folder 50)
  - Item 1: Handicapped Workers, 1958; Publication (Box 29, Folder 50)
- Box: 29, Folder: 51, Publication (Box 29, Folder 51)
  - Item 1: Handicapped Workers, 1957; Publication (Box 29, Folder 51)
- Box: 29, Folder: 52, Publication (Box 29, Folder 52)
  - Item 1: Rating Executives, 1960; Publication (Box 29, Folder 52)
- Box: 29, Folder: 53, Publication (Box 29, Folder 53)
  - Item 1: Employee Aptitude Survey, 1957; Publication (Box 29, Folder 53)
- Box: 29, Folder: 54, Publication (Box 29, Folder 54)
  - Item 1: Employee Recruiting, 1968; Publication (Box 29, Folder 54)
- Box: 29, Folder: 55, Publication (Box 29, Folder 55)
  - Item 1: Business And Politics, 1958; Publication (Box 29, Folder 55)
- Box: 29, Folder: 56, Publication (Box 29, Folder 56)
  - Item 1: Public Relations, 1958; Publication (Box 29, Folder 56)
- Box: 29, Folder: 57, Publication (Box 29, Folder 57)
  - Item 1: Employee Recruiting, 1960; Publication (Box 29, Folder 57)
- Box: 29, Folder: 58, Publication (Box 29, Folder 58)
  - Item 1: A Description of Major Functions And Activities, 1956; Publication (Box 29, Folder 58)
- Box: 29, Folder: 59, Publication (Box 29, Folder 59)
  - Item 1: Security Manual, 1959; Publication (Box 29, Folder 59)
- Box: 29, Folder: 60, Publication (Box 29, Folder 60)
  - Item 1: Industrial Relations Directives, 1950; Publication (Box 29, Folder 60)
- Box: 29, Folder: 61, Publication (Box 29, Folder 61)
  - Item 1: Accident Prevention, 1960; Publication (Box 29, Folder 61)
- Box: 29, Folder: 62, Publication (Box 29, Folder 62)
  - Item 1: Quality Assurance Training Plan, 1972; Publication (Box 29, Folder 62)
- Box: 29, Folder: 63, Publication (Box 29, Folder 63)
  - Item 1: Handbook, 1966; Publication (Box 29, Folder 63)
- Box: 29, Folder: 64, Publication (Box 29, Folder 64)
  - Item 1: Development Appraisals, 1966; Publication (Box 29, Folder 64)
- Box: 29, Folder: 65, Publication (Box 29, Folder 65)
  - Item 1: Employee Recruiting, 1972; Publication (Box 29, Folder 65)
- Box: 29, Folder: 66, Publication (Box 29, Folder 66)
  - Item 1: Industrial Education, 1963; Publication (Box 29, Folder 66)
- Box: 29, Folder: 67, Publication (Box 29, Folder 67)
  - Item 1: Course Announcement: Spring 1972, Publication (Box 29, Folder 67)
- Box: 29, Folder: 68, Publication (Box 29, Folder 68)
  - Item 1: Supervisor-Operations Selection Study, 1969; Publication (Box 29, Folder 68)
- Box: 29, Folder: 69, Publication (Box 29, Folder 69)
  - Item 1: Industrial Organization, 1972; Publication (Box 29, Folder 69)
- Box: 29, Folder: 70, Publication (Box 29, Folder 70)
  - Item 1: Summary of Changes In Bargaining Agreement, 1971; Publication (Box 29, Folder 70)
- Box: 29, Folder: 71, Publication (Box 29, Folder 71)
  - Item 1: Industrial Organization, 1972; Publication (Box 29, Folder 71)
- Box: 29, Folder: 72, Publication (Box 29, Folder 72)
  - Item 1: Checklist Of Material Needed On Company Industrial Relations Activities, 1966; Publication (Box 29, Folder 72)
- Box: 29, Folder: 73, Publication (Box 29, Folder 73)
  - Item 1: Industrial Relations, 1972; Publication (Box 29, Folder 73)
- Box: 29, Folder: 74, Publication (Box 29, Folder 74)
  - Item 1: Major Lockheed Activities, 1972; Publication (Box 29, Folder 74)
- Box: 29, Folder: 75, Publication (Box 29, Folder 75)
  - Item 1: Management Development Seminars, 1971; Publication (Box 29, Folder 75)
- Box: 29, Folder: 76, Publication (Box 29, Folder 76)
  - Item 1: Synopsis of Arbitration Cases, 1972; Publication (Box 29, Folder 76)
- Box: 29, Folder: 77, Publication (Box 29, Folder 77)
  - Item 1: Standard Practice Instruction, 1965; Publication (Box 29, Folder 77)
- Box: 29, Folder: 78, Publication (Box 29, Folder 78)
  - Item 1: New Employees Traveling and Money Expense, 1965; Publication (Box 29, Folder 78)
- Box: 29, Folder: 79, Publication (Box 29, Folder 79)
  - Item 1: Working Hours For Female Non-exempt Employees, 1963; Publication (Box 29, Folder 79)
- Box: 29, Folder: 80, Publication (Box 29, Folder 80)
  - Item 1: Employee Recruiting, 1966; Publication (Box 29, Folder 80)
- Box: 29, Folder: 81, Publication (Box 29, Folder 81)
  - Item 1: Employee Recruiting, 1966; Publication (Box 29, Folder 81)
- Box: 29, Folder: 82, Publication (Box 29, Folder 82)
  - Item 1: Management Ready Reserves Program, 1966; Publication (Box 29, Folder 82)
- Box: 29, Folder: 83, Publication (Box 29, Folder 83)
  - Item 1: Elements of Supervision, 1966; Publication (Box 29, Folder 83)
- Box: 29, Folder: 84, Publication (Box 29, Folder 84)
  - Item 1: Management Development, 1966; Publication (Box 29, Folder 84)
- Box: 29, Folder: 85, Publication (Box 29, Folder 85)
  - Item 1: Management Workshop, 1966; Publication (Box 29, Folder 85)
- Box: 29, Folder: 86, Publication (Box 29, Folder 86)
  - Item 1: Industrial Organization Chart, 1966; Publication (Box 29, Folder 86)